silk.com 2016-05-05

# WhiteWave Foods

**Last Updated: April 22nd, 2015**

This Privacy Policy applies to your use of the following WhiteWave Foods Company websites: [www.whitewave.com](http://www.whitewave.com/), [www.horizondairy.com](http://www.horizondairy.com/), www.internationaldelight.com, [www.silk.com](http://www.silk.com/), [www.sodeliciousdairyfree.com](http://sodeliciousdairyfree.com/), [www.bonzayogurt.com](http://www.bonzayogurt.com/), and [www.yuluyogurt.com](http://www.yuluyogurt.com/) (each a “Site” and collectively the “Sites”). WhiteWave Foods strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness, and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, WhiteWave Foods is dedicated to protecting your privacy through compliance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy describes the type of information we may collect from you or that you may provide to us when you visit a Site. Your use of a Site indicates your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Sites or any services available on or through the Sites.

**Personal Information**  
WhiteWave Foods may collect personally identifiable information from you, meaning information about you that can be used to contact or uniquely identify you (“Personal Information”), only on a voluntary basis. Such Personal Information may include information such as your name, postal address, email address, company name, and telephone number.

We collect Personal Information from you if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, or sign up to join our email lists. Personal Information we collect is internally reviewed and used to improve our Sites, to notify you of updates to our Sites or any products or services we offer, to respond to visitor inquiries, to carry out our obligations and enforce our rights, and to fulfill any other purpose for which you provide your Personal Information to us. Once your Personal Information is reviewed, it is either discarded or stored in our files.

If you supply us with your postal address, you will receive only the information you request at the time you provide your postal address to us. Your Personal Information, including without limitation your postal address, will not be sold or provided to third parties except as set forth in this Privacy Policy. We will seek to obtain written or active email consent from you if we intend to use information collected from you in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection.

**Non-Personal Information**  
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable, including through automated means such as cookies. A “cookie” is a text file that websites send to a user’s computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the user’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. For example, our Sites may automatically recognize the domain name of the website, or the advertisement, which referred you to one of our Sites (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account). Cookies enable us to track things in aggregate form such as the total number of visitors to our Sites, the popularity of various areas of our Sites, and the length of the visits to our Sites. No Personal Information is extracted in this process. The information we collect using automated means is used for internal review to improve the Sites, and is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

**Information We Share**  
In order to improve our business, we may buy or sell a company, or one or more of the companies in our corporate family may merge with or be acquired by another company. If we sell a business, we may transfer some or all of your information as a part of the sale. In the event we transfer any of your information in connection with such a sale, we will post a notice on our website and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser of your information honors your opt-out requests, if any.

We may disclose your Personal Information to our contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep Personal Information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.  
We may also disclose your Personal Information when we believe it is necessary and appropriate to comply with applicable laws or to protect the rights, property or safety of WhiteWave Foods, our employees, customers, Site visitors, or others.

Other than as set forth above, we will not share or sell your information to any outside organization without your written or electronically-indicated consent.  
Your Choices If you do not wish for us to use your Personal Information to send you promotions regarding our products or services, you can opt out of such use by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your Personal Information or at any other time by sending an email to Direct Partners at WhiteWave@WhiteWaveMemberSupport.com stating your request. If we have sent you a promotional email, you may choose not to receive further promotional emails from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of such email.

Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all of our Sites’ features.

**How You Can Correct or Remove Information**  
If you have submitted Personal Information to us and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please click on the applicable “Contact Us” link below and contact us as indicated.You can also send an email to Direct Partners at WhiteWave@WhiteWaveMemberSupport.com for this purpose. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to make corrections or remove your Personal Information from our records.

**Children Under the Age of 13**  
Our Sites are not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information or other information from children under age 13. If you are under 13 years old, do not use or provide any information on or through the Sites. If we learn we have collected or received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any Personal Information from or about a child under the age of 13, please contact Direct Partners at WhiteWave@WhiteWaveMemberSupport.com.

**Updates and Effective Date**  
WhiteWave Foods reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our Sites that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new policy. In the event we make a material change to how we use your Personal Information, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of such new or different use. The date the Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of this page. You are responsible for periodically reviewing our Sites and this Privacy Policy to check for any updates or changes.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please write, phone or email us via the contact information below: 

WhiteWave Foods Company  
Consumer Affairs   
12002 Airport Way   
Broomfield, CO 80021 

Phone Toll Free 1-888-820-9283

Contact Us Online:  

©2015 WhiteWave Foods Company. All Rights Reserved.
